http://www.nvish.com/privacy-policy

Our Privacy Policy is Transparent
NVISH is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Our privacy policy is transparent, we do not collect/store your personal information, when you visit our website(s), unless you volunteer to provide that information to us.
The following provides an overview of how we protect your privacy during your visit, and handle the information we gather.
Information on our website(s) is gathered in two ways:
Information stored automatically (for example, through our site's technology); and
Information collected with consent (for example, when you voluntarily provide information).
Information Collected and Stored Automatically
We collect information from you, when you visit our website(s), to browse, read, or download information. Even if you do not register for any of our services, we gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and/or to administer our web site. This helps us identify the pages which our users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information. This implies we track users' sessions but not the users. The users remain anonymous.
The kind of information that we may gather automatically includes the type of browser you are using (e.g. Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of Operating System you are using (e.g. Windows 98, XP, Windows Vista, Windows 7 or Mac OS) or the domain name of your Internet Service Provider (e.g. AOL, Comcast, VSNL, etc.), the date and time of your visit, and the pages you visit. We utilize this non-personally identifiable information to primarily improve our website(s) design, content, and your browsing experience.
This site may contain links to other sites. NVISH is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.
Personal Information Collected with Consent
We collect your personal information, only if you provide it voluntarily. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include name, address, E-mail address, and information about your interests in using various services. For example, you might submit your name and e-mail address to subscribe to any of our services, or to ask for a quote, or to send us your feedback. The information you provide is not given or sold to any private organizations or person.
